# **Angelo Bryan**

Web Developer

As a web developer with former experience in digital marketing, specifically in designing websites and SEO, I believe in constantly improving. I currently have experience in Django Rest Framework and React, but can't wait to learn more!

#### CONTACT

(402)218-3590

≥ alobryan2@gmail.com

Wake Forest, NC

in www.linkedIn.com/in/angelo-bryan

https://github.com/Ambryan 2

## **EDUCATION**

### **Software Developer**

Momentum Sept 2022 - Jan 2023

#### **Bachelor's Degree**

Business Administration, Marketing North Carolina State University, Aug 2018 - Dec 2021

#### **SKILLS**

- Python
- JavaScript
- Django
- React
- Git
- Html/CSS
- PostgreSql
- Agile

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Full Stack Web Developer**

Momentum | September 2022 - January 2023

- Used Django Rest Framework and React to build out an application
- Learned about Agile principles and implemented them in a group project
- Used JavaScript, Python, Html, and CSS to build applications

#### Web Design Apprentice

BasantNow | August 2022 - October 2022

- Designed a Brilliant Directories site using HTML, CSS, and site widgets
- Conducted Keyword Research that increased traffic by 10% on pages
- Used Adobe Photoshop to create thumbnails for Youtube Channel

## **Safety Intern**

Lake Cable LLC | Summer 2021

- Managed wire samples using excel to increase organization and disposed of wire that did not pass through quality inspection
- Organized records of the processes that went on throughout the plant

## **Account Manager/Consultant**

CMS Consulting | February-December 2020

- Led a team of 5 to design a campaign that led to the doubling of current members for our client
- Conducted research on the best social media practices in order to drive up engagement and awareness for our client
- Captured and edited photos for use on the client's website

# **Projects**

# NeoSelf / Project Link

- Full Stack app that helps users stick to their new Habits
- On the backend I was able to populate multiple models off of a single instance. On the front end, I was able to parse the data I made on the backend to make charts for the user to see.